[
  {
    "question": "Everything in React is a......?",
    "opt1": "Module",
    "opt2": "Component",
    "opt3": "Package",
    "opt4": "Class",
    "answer": "Component"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which directory React Components are saved ?",
    "opt1": "Inside js/components/",
    "opt2": "Inside vendor/components/",
    "opt3": "Inside external/components/",
    "opt4": "Inside vendor/",
    "answer": "Inside js/components/"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many elements does a react component return ? ",
    "opt1": "2 Elements",
    "opt2": "1 Element",
    "opt3": "Multiple Elements",
    "opt4": "None of These",
    "answer": "Multiple Elements"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is state in React?",
    "opt1": "A persistant storage.",
    "opt2": "An internal data store (object) of a component.",
    "opt3": "we can pass date to other component",
    "opt4": "A and B",
    "answer": "An internal data store (object) of a component."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Babel?",
    "opt1": "A transpiler.",
    "opt2": "An interpreter",
    "opt3": "A Compiler",
    "opt4": "Both Compiler and Transpilar",
    "answer": "Both Compiler and Transpilar"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does webpack command do?",
    "opt1": "Transpiles all the Javascript down into one file",
    "opt2": "Runs react local development server.",
    "opt3": "A module bundler",
    "opt4": "All above",
    "answer": "A module bundler"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Reactjs",
    "opt1": "Server side Framework",
    "opt2": "User-interface framework",
    "opt3": "A Library for building interaction interfaces",
    "opt4": "None of These",
    "answer": "A Library for building interaction interfaces"
  },
  {
    "question": "In react, what is used to pass data to a component from outside ?",
    "opt1": "setState",
    "opt2": "render with arguments",
    "opt3": "props",
    "opt4": "PropTypes",
    "answer": "props"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reactjs uses .... to increase performance?",
    "opt1": "Original DOM",
    "opt2": "Virtual DOM",
    "opt3": "Both 1 & 2",
    "opt4": "None of above",
    "answer": "Virtual DOM"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of React.js Developer ?",
    "opt1": "Jordan mike",
    "opt2": "Jordan Lee",
    "opt3": "Jordan Walke",
    "opt4": "Tim Lee",
    "answer": "Jordan Walke"
  }
]
